compareyourfare.com 2016-12-01

# Privacy Policy

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first our Chief Privacy Officer at privacy@compareyourfare.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

Compareyourfare.com understands that making a purchase online involves a great deal of trust on your part. Your trust is extremely important to us and as such, we make it our highest priority to ensure that we have implemented information handling practices consistent with the highest standards and best practices of organizations currently doing business on the Internet. 

As a visitor to our web site, you have the right to understand our information privacy practices prior to providing Compareyourfare.com with any of your personally identifiable information ("PII"). This privacy policy describes the practices that apply to our site, including specifically:

**What personal information is being gathered about you?**

Compareyourfare.com collects personally identifiable information ("PII") that you specifically and voluntarily provide. "PII" includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name, phone number, or e-mail address. If you or the third party no longer wish to receive our newsletters and promotional communications, please notify us immediately at helpdesk@travelsupport.com or simply click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any promotional e-mail blast. You may also delete third party profiles at any time. 

**How is this infomation being gathered?**

Although you are not required to register as a member of Compareyourfare.com, many areas of Compareyourfare.com can be accessed without providing any PII. Compareyourfare.com collects PII when you: 

  * Purchase Travel
  * Contact Compareyourfare.com
  * Opt-in to receive e-mail travel specials

**Purchase Travel**

Compareyourfare.com collects the billing address of the credit card that is used to purchase travel. We will also collect credit card information, including card number, card type, cardholder name, and expiration date, in order to bill you for travel purchased through Compareyourfare.com. Please view our Credit Card Guarantee for additional information on our commitment to protecting your credit card security. 

**Contact CompareYourFare**

CompareYourFare collects PII such as your full name, Member ID, e-mail address, and/or contact number whenever you submit a question or suggestion, or request assistance with viewing your itinerary, logging on to Compareyourfare.com, or accessing your account. This information is not stored anywhere on our site and is used solely to help us respond to your questions. 

**Opt-in to receive email travel specials**

To participate in our free email program, Compareyourfare.com will collect email addresses, and other pertinent demographic information from you (such as personal travel interests). This information is used strictly for the purposes of sending relevant news and content to you. 

**Who do we share your information with?**

Compareyourfare.com may share your information with suppliers such as hotel, airline, cruise, car rental companies, or activity providers, who fulfill your travel reservations. We do not share your email address with these suppliers unless they need it to fulfill the travel reservation you have made on Compareyourfare.com, and will restrict their use of this information for that purpose only. Please note that these suppliers also may contact you as necessary to obtain additional information about you or to facilitate your travel reservation. 

Third Party Vendors Compareyourfare.com may share your information with third party vendors who provide services or functions on our behalf, including credit card processing, business analytics, customer service, marketing, distribution of e-mails or surveys, and fraud prevention. These companies have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use the information for any other purpose. 

We may also use your information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. If we believe it necessary to defend the rights, property, or safety of Compareyourfare.com, our customers, or others, we will use your information as needed to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities. 

**How is this information being used?**

When you purchase through Compareyourfare.com or opt-in to receive our emails, we will collect personal information that is necessary for us to provide you with the services offered on our site. As mentioned, this information may include personal items such as your name, e-mail and mailing address and telephone number. You may also have to provide a valid e-mail address and select a password that will be required to gain access to select portions of our site. 

We will also use your e-mail address or telephone number to respond when you submit a question, request assistance or need to access your account information.

**Will this information be shared with anyone?**

When you reserve or purchase travel services through Compareyourfare.com, we must provide certain information about you to the airline, car-rental agency, hotel, travel agency or other involved third party to ensure the successful fulfillment of your travel arrangements. 

We do not sell individual customer names or other private profile information to third parties

**Cookies and Other Web Technologies**

When you visit Compareyourfare.com, we may assign your computer a “cookie” (a small, unique identifier text file stored by your web browser on your computer’s hard drive). For example, whenever you sign in as a Smartafres.com member, we record your member ID and the name on your member account in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you checked the box entitled “Remember me next time.” Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our site. 

The use of cookies is very common on the Internet and Compareyourfare.com’s use of cookies is very similar to that of Expedia and Travelocity, as well as Yahoo! and CNN.com. Cookies are unable to do such things as run programs on your computer or plant viruses. 

Note that member IDs, passwords, and any other account-related data in such cookies are encrypted for security purposes. No personal information about you is gathered or stored in the cookies placed by the ComareYourFare.com web site. You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie. Please note that if you refuse to accept from Compareyourfare.com, you may not be able to access many of the travel tools offered by CompareYourFare.com 

**How We Protect Your Information?**

Compareyourfare.com is committed to safeguarding your personal and confidential information. For that reason, we employ a staff of security technology professionals and utilize a full range of the best security technology available. Specifically, your information is secured from unauthorized access from the Internet through market leading firewall technology. We also protect the connection between your computer and our server from eavesdropping through industry-standard encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL). Depending on your browser, this SSL will have encryption keys of up to 128 bits. To ensure that we fulfill our commitment to safeguard your information, we continually assess new technology for protecting your information to make sure that our information handling practices are in accordance with the highest industry standards and best practices on the Internet at all times. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy or our information handling practices, you may contact our Chief Privacy Officer at helpdesk@travelsupport.com. We will attempt to respond to your questions or concerns within two (2) business days after we receive them. You may also write to us in care of Compareyourfare.com, 350 Tenth Ave, Suite 1200, San Diego, CA, 92101. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Compareyourfare.com may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the e-mail address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our Web site. 

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 30, 2008**
